bbcanada.com 2006-12-07

# Privacy Bed and Breakfasts: Privacy Bed and Breakfast Accommodation B&Bs

**BBCanada.com**  
**Privacy Policy Statement**

Bed & Breakfast Online Canada Inc. ("BBC") is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information collected at this Web site at www.bbcanada.com (the "Web site").

**Collection of Information**

Before BBC collects your personal information, you will be told (in this Privacy Policy Statement or at the time such information is collected) the purpose(s) for which such information will be used, and will have the choice of whether to provide such information to BBC. If you choose not to provide such information, you may not be able to access certain materials on this Web site.

We require you to provide personal information such as your name and contact information (including e-mail address, mailing address or other similar information) in order to participate in sweepstakes sponsored from time to time by BBC and its co-sponsors, if any (the "Sponsors") for the purposes of (i) administering such sweepstakes and (ii) communicating with you in the future about Sponsors' products and promotions. By providing your personal information to BBC in order to participate in a sweepstakes, you consent to BBC disclosing your personal information to other Sponsors and/or their promotional agencies, and to the Sponsors and/or their promotional agencies storing and using your personal information for the purpose of communicating with you in the future regarding their products and promotions. If you do not wish to continue receiving such communications, you can opt-out at any time by following the opt-out procedures provided in such communications or by contacting us at the e-mail address, postal address or telephone number listed below.

**Use, Disclosure, and Transfer of Personal Information**

BBC will collect, use, store, maintain, transfer, and delete your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy Statement. BBC will disclose your personal information to outside organizations only with your consent, unless disclosing such information is required by applicable law, statute, regulation, ordinance, or court order or BBC has reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the rules and regulations of a sweepstakes or may be causing injury to or interference with BBC or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Where BBC does disclose your personal information to BBC business partners, which may include co-sponsors suppliers and promotional agencies, BBC will advise you of such proposed disclosure and require them to agree to use such personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy Statement and only for the purposes for which the information was collected. The disclosure of personal information as contemplated in this Privacy Policy Statement may be to a party outside of your home jurisdiction, including to jurisdictions that may have different laws and rules to protect personal information.

**Accessing, Modifying, or Removing Your Information**

Under applicable laws, you may have the right to inquire whether BBC holds personal information about you and a limited right to access such personal information and correct any inaccurate information. If the information you provide changes or becomes inaccurate, or if you would like to delete your information from the BBC database, please contact us at the e-mail address, postal address, or telephone number listed below.

**Information Security**

When you provide personal information to us, such information is stored electronically on secured servers located in Ontario, Canada. BBC takes reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss and unauthorized use, and to delete, destroy or make anonymous your personal information when it is no longer required for its intended purposes. BBC cannot, however, guarantee that loss or unauthorized use will never occur (e.g., that someone will not overcome our security measures), and makes no representations or warranties to this effect.

**A Special Note To Parents**

We respect the privacy of all of our online users, especially children. We do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. We encourage parents to monitor, supervise and join their children in online activities.

**Questions**

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please contact:

Bed & Breakfast Online Canada, Inc.  
361 Jackson Street West, Suite 209  
Hamilton, ON., L8P 1N2  
Canada

We can also be reached via e-mail at [info@bbcanada.com](mailto:info@bbcanada.com) or by telephone at 800-239-1141.

BBC reserves the right to use non-personal and aggregated information (information that is not individually identifiable). Such aggregate uses could include, but are not limited to improving the operation, quality and security of the Web site. We may also use cookies to make our Web site more user friendly and personalize the content that is delivered to you.

This Web site may contain links to third-party Web sites. This Privacy Policy Statement does not apply to and BBC is not responsible for the privacy practices, content, or conduct related to and on such Web sites.

BBC may change this Privacy Policy Statement from time to time. If this Privacy Policy Statement changes, the revised policy will be accessible via the Privacy link on this BBC Web site.

Revised: July 23, 2004
